[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Its your Birthday, and youre in Tokyo. Later that calendar day, you board a flight for Los Angeles. Will you be able to celebrate your birthday twice?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dram is the monetary unit of this country whose capital city is Yerevan.", "correct_answer": "Armenia", "incorrect_answers": ["Moldova", "Azerbaijan", "Andorra"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can polar bears be other colors besides white?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jurassic Park was built on a secluded island in this country.", "correct_answer": "Costa Rica", "incorrect_answers": ["Panama", "Brazil", "Belize"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Enos drops Annie off at the crossroads in the film Friday the 13th, how far does she walk to get to Camp Crystal Lake?", "correct_answer": "none of these", "incorrect_answers": ["5 miles", "10 miles", "15 miles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The flag of which of the countries listed below is not red and white?", "correct_answer": "Jamaica", "incorrect_answers": ["Poland", "Turkey", "Japan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the position number of a Center in basketball?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["1", "3", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This film term is defined as a type of filmic organization in which the parts relate to each other through a series of causally related events taking place in time and space.", "correct_answer": "Narrative", "incorrect_answers": ["Story", "Plot", "Screenplay"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which battleship was used by the US Navy during World War II, the Korean War, and the Vietnam War?", "correct_answer": "USS New Jersey (BB-62)", "incorrect_answers": ["USS Arizona (BB-39)", "USS Missouri (BB-63)", "USS Iowa (BB-61)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the comedy movie Norbit, what business are the Latimores in?", "correct_answer": "Construction", "incorrect_answers": ["FBI", "Sports Agents", "Banking"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was/were the first victim(s) of the snakes in the movie Snakes on a Plane?", "correct_answer": "a couple having sex in a bathroom", "incorrect_answers": ["a man urinating in a bathroom", "a flight attendant", "the planes captain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a caterpillar turn into?", "correct_answer": "butterfly or moth", "incorrect_answers": ["butterfly", "moth", "larva"]}]